export default data = [
  (type1 = [
    {
      question: 'A girl is riding a _____.',
      options: ['like', 'bike', 'hike'],
      correct_option: 'bike',
    },
    {
      question: 'A boy is playing with a _____.',
      options: ['ball', 'tall', 'call'],
      correct_option: 'ball',
    },
    {
      question: 'A  _____ is sleeping under the table.',
      options: ['pat', 'cat', 'bat'],
      correct_option: 'cat',
    },
    {
      question: 'The dog chased the _____.',
      options: ['fog', 'log', 'frog'],
      correct_option: 'frog',
    },
    {
      question: 'The kids love to ____ in the park.',
      options: ['run', 'fun', 'bun'],
      correct_option: 'run',
    },
  ]),
  (type2 = [
    {
      question: 'She met her _____ at the _____.',
      options: ['bad, park', 'dad, qark', 'dad, park'],
      correct_option: 'dad, park',
    },
    {
      question: 'She saw a _____ at the _____.',
      options: ['pig, park', 'pig, qark', 'qig, park'],
      correct_option: 'pig, park',
    },
    {
      question: 'The _____ are passing the _____.',
      options: ['boys, ball', 'doys, ball', 'boys, dall'],
      correct_option: 'boys, ball',
    },
    {
      question: 'He found his _____ at the _____.',
      options: ['hat, lake', 'cat, wake', 'hat, wake'],
      correct_option: 'hat, lake',
    },
    {
      question: 'The _____ is flying near the _____.',
      options: ['kite, tree', 'kight, tree', 'kite, flee'],
      correct_option: 'kite, tree',
    },
  ]),
  (type3 = [
    {
      question: 'He _____ homework.',
      options: ['does', 'dose', 'doos'],
      correct_option: 'does',
    },
    {
      question: 'she asked _____ for homework.',
      options: ['hlep', 'help', 'hlpe'],
      correct_option: 'help',
    },
    {
      question: 'Family ____ the presents carefully.',
      options: ['wrap', 'warp', 'wrape'],
      correct_option: 'wrap',
    },
    {
      question: 'She needs to _____ the book.',
      options: ['read', 'reed', 'reid'],
      correct_option: 'read',
    },
    {
      question: 'He is learning to ____ a bike.',
      options: ['ride', 'ried', 'ryde'],
      correct_option: 'ride',
    },
  ]),
  (type4 = [
    {
      question: 'I have a 5 year old _____.',
      options: ['son', 'sun'],
      correct_option: 'son',
    },
    {
      question: 'They parked the car ____ the store.',
      options: ['by', 'buy', 'bye'],
      correct_option: 'by',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mother asked, ____ broke the vase?',
      options: ['how', 'who'],
      correct_option: 'who',
    },
    {
      question: 'The teacher said ____ are late.',
      options: ['you', 'yew', 'your'],
      correct_option: 'you',
    },
    {
      question: 'Please hand me ____ pencil.',
      options: ['my', 'me', 'mine'],
      correct_option: 'my',
    },
  ]),
  (type5 = [
    {
      question: 'She felt a _____ in her leg.',
      options: ['pane', 'pain'],
      correct_option: 'pain',
    },
    {
      question: 'He hates to ____ the loud noises.',
      options: ['hear', 'here'],
      correct_option: 'hear',
    },
    {
      question: 'Kids are walking to ____ house after school.',
      options: ['their', 'there'],
      correct_option: 'their',
    },
    {
      question: 'He likes to _____ music.',
      options: ['hear', 'here'],
      correct_option: 'hear',
    },
    {
      question: 'The cat is sleeping in ____ basket.',
      options: ['its', 'itse'],
      correct_option: 'its',
    },
  ]),
];
